# JAKE ROD

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am an adaptive Full-Stack Web & Mobile Developer with experience in JavaScript (including ¡Query, React, & Node.js), HTML/CSS, and Python. I am a guick learner with a passion for problem solving and a drive to bring projects to completion.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### IT TECHNICIAN

Hollywood Casino, Aurora, IL / Mar 2020 - Jan 2021

• Provided low to mid-level technical support to maintain casino operations. Highly involved with AS400, Active Directory, MySQL, Remote Desktop, Server Analysis.

#### **CLAIMS ASSOCIATE**

State Farm, Bloomington, IL / Mar 2019 - Jul 2019

• Used enterprise software systems to investigate, evaluate, negotiate, and settle auto claims.

#### **CLAIMS SPECIALIST**

Aloha Construction, Bloomington, IL / Mar 2018 - Jan 2019

• Door-to-door roofing sales in storm-affected areas.

#### LAWN CARE SPECIALIST

Trugreen, Rochelle, IL / Mar 2017 - Jul 2017

• Sales, Customer Service, Pesticide Application.

## SALES ASSOCIATE; DEPARTMENT MANAGER

MC Sports, Peru, IL / May 2014 - Jul 2016

• Sales, Customer Service. Oversaw all inventory of shoe department.

### **BOYS' BASKETBALL COACH**

Northbrook Middle School, Mendota, IL / Oct 2015 - Mar 2016

• Head Coach, in charge of all practice scheduling, planning, and responsible for all players on game day.

- (815) 910-2820
- **9** 32752 2660 North Avenue, LaMoille, IL, 61330

## **EDUCATION**

## NUCAMP CODING **BOOTCAMP** Aurora, IL

Web Development Certificate (Expected graduation Aug 2021) Relevant Coursework

- Responsive with Bootstrap
- Dynamic with React
- Mobile with React-Native
- Backend with Node.js/MongoDB/Express

## ILLINOIS VALLEY COMMUNITY COLLEGE Oglesby, IL

Completed coursework towards Associate in Science (A.S.) Biology (May 2016)

## ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Front-End Software Development-Javascript / React / React-Native / Bootstrap / HTML/CSS

Back-End Software Development-Node.js / MongoDB / Express / Python / AWS

#### CERTIFICATIONS

Future Web Development **Bootcamp Graduate**